Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- John Tower Years, 1977-2012, undated; 4
  - Trip to West Point, Biographical Materials, Itineraries, and Photographs (1 of 2), 1981-1982, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Trip to West Point, Biographical Materials, Itineraries, and Photographs (2 of 2), 1981-1982, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Senate Armed Services Christmas Party, Photographs, 1981 December (Box 7, Folder 1)
- John Warner Years, 1968-2012, undated; 5
  Series V. John Warner Years consists of correspondence, photographs, programs, and other materials compiled during Mattie McKee’s employment as the Executive Assistant to Republican Senator John Warner of Virginia. McKee worked for Senator Warner from January 1985 to April 1989 at which point McKee left Washington, D.C. and returned to her home state of Texas. The materials in this series are in good condition.
  - 3rd Annual John Warner Invitational Golf and Tennis Classic Awards Dinner, Program, 1985 June 22 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 4th Annual Benefit for the Washington Home, Program, 1985 November 21-25 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 99th Congress, Program, 1985 September 10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 100th Congress, Guide to the Senate, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Article, “The Inside Story”, Washington Dossier, 1985 March (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Article, “Senatorial Dossier”, Washington Dossier, 1985 May (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Atoka Farm, Articles and Notes, 1970-1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Change of Command Ceremony on the U.S.S. Barry, Program, 1988 September 18 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, General, 2003-2009 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Staff Club, Certificate, 1987 May (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, General (1 of 3), 1985-2004, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, General (2 of 3), 1985-2004, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, General (3 of 3), 1985-2004, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Area Church of Christ Congressional Breakfasts, Correspondence, 1988-2008, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 1985-1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - John Warner, Biographical Materials, circa 2009 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - National Symphony Orchestra Ball, Program, 1988 December (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Rosters, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, General (1 of 2), 1986-1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, General (2 of 2), 1986-1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ronald and Nancy Reagan, Christmas Cards, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - The Texas Navy, Book, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam War Memorial, Notes on Construction, 1989-2012 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Victor and Laurene-Anne Sherlock, Correspondence, Photographs, and Programs, 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Personal, 1948-2018, undated; 6
  Series VI. Personal consists primarily of materials Mattie McKee accumulated after leaving her career in Washington, D.C. in 1989. Personal correspondence, a disassembled scrapbook, and documents relating to her 2014 book, In the Shadow of the Greats: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle, feature prominently. Overall, this series is in good condition.
  - Albert S. Nemir, Obituary, Congressional Record, 1985 March 28 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Book, In the Shadow of the Greats: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chuck Yeager, Photographs and Press Releases, 1948-1963, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, General, 1990-2016, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Responses to In the Shadow of the Greats (1 of 2), 2014-2016 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Responses to In the Shadow of the Greats (2 of 2), 2014-2016 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth M. Cordes, Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - George W. Bush Presidential Campaign, Thank You Note, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 1984-2007 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Menard Library Club Luncheon, Clipping, 2015 March 12 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mildred Kitka, Correspondence, Obituaries, and Photographs, 1987-2013, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Nemir Family Reunions, Correspondence and Photographs, 1979-2012 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Articles by Mike Cochran Regarding Mattie McKee’s Career, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Notes, 1989-2008, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Photographs Used in In the Shadow of the Greats, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Roll Call, Periodical, Special 35th Anniversary Section, 1990 June 18 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook (Disassembled) [Pages 1-5], 1977-1978 April (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (Disassembled) [Pages 6-11], 1978 November-1983 November (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (Disassembled) [Pages 12-16], 1983 December-1986 November (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook (Disassembled) [Pages 17-20], 1987 November-1989 November (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Speaking Engagements, Photographs and Speeches, 2007-2018 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Texas State Society, Black Tie and Boots Inaugural Ball, Invitations and Photographs, 2001-2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Texas State Society, Brochures, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Texas State Society, Invitation and Newsletters, 1985-2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)